Alright, awesome. So now that we know more about how to get unblocked, we can move on.
太好了，现在我们已经知道了该如何解决遇到的问题，可以继续了
The reason it's so important to learn how to get unblocked is because
学习如何解决问题如此重要的原因是因为
blockchain and web three is more than just everybody on their own.
区块链和 web3 并不仅仅是每个人自己的东西
It is a very collaborative space.
它是一个合作化程度很高的空间
So as you get better, and as you learn more
所以当你学得更多，学得更好的时候
a massive way to test how much you've learned and give back to the community
一个测试你学到了多少并回馈社区的重要方式就是
is to going to Stack Overflow and going to stack exchange them
去 Stack Overflow 和 Stack Exchange
and trying to answer some questions yourself.
并尝试自己解答一些问题
So I highly recommend you all go to Stack Overflow,
所以我强烈推荐你们都去用用 Stack Overflow
and then you go to the GitHub repo associated with the scores,
然后你可以去与本课程关联的 Github 仓库
you try to answer some discussions, try to answer some issues and help other people out
试着回答一些讨论，解答一些问题并帮助其他人
because it's going to help you become a much better software engineer.
因为这能帮你成为一个更优秀的软件工程师
The other reason I want to do that part is because
我想做这个部分的另一个原因是
when we install some of the tools that I'm about to show you,
当我们安装我向你展示的某些工具时
sometimes the installation process is the hardest piece there.
有时安装过程反而是最难的部分
Once you get past the install process,
一旦完成了安装，
it generally becomes much, much easier.
通常就会变得容易许多
But this can often be the hardest part of the course is
但往往课程中最难的部分就是
just installing some of these tools that we're going to give you.
安装好我告诉你的这些工具
And that's what we're going to learn about right now.
而这就是我们现在马上要学的东西
So we have been working so far with remix, remix IDE, or integrated development environment.
到目前为止我们一直在使用 Remix，Remix IDE，或者说集成开发环境(IDE)
As we've seen, it's this wonderful place
正如我们所看到的，这是一个很棒的地方
where we can try out code we can try solidity out,
在这里我们可以尝试代码，尝试 solidity
we can compile we can deploy, we can pretty much do everything that we need to do.
可以编译，可以部署，我们几乎可以做我们需要做的一切事情
It's web based. It can do testing, debugging, deploying local JavaScript VM,
它是以 web 为基础的，可以做测试，调试 bug，部署本地 JavaScript VM
it's very quick and easy to create and test our smart contracts.
这一个非常快速且容易地创建和测试我们智能合约的方式
However, it does have some limitations.
然而，它也有一些局限性
It can really only deal with smart contract,
它只能处理智能合约
it can't really integrate with other parts of projects.
不能真正地与项目的其他部分集成
It has limited support for tests or custom deployments.
它对测试和定制部署的支持有限
And you need an internet connection to even work with remix
并且你甚至还需要保持联网才能使用 Remix
and it can be tricky to do a lot more advanced functionality.
要想实现更高级的功能也比较麻烦
So it's a phenomenal tool and absolutely if you're looking to do something very quickly,
所以，这确实是一个很棒的工具，如果你要快速实现某件事
I absolutely recommend everybody just go to remix to go ahead and try something out
那我强烈建议你使用 Remix 进行各种尝试
how are now we're going to move over to
然而，我们现在要转而使用
a more professional smart contract developer setup.
一种更为专业的智能合约开发者配置
And this is with hard hat.
它的名字是 Hardhat
This is known as a smart contract developer framework
这就是所谓的智能合约开发框架
similar to brownie or foundry or, and likes, there's a number of these frameworks.
它就和 Brownie 或 Foundry 类似，有很多这样的框架
And the reason that we're going to do hard hat is because hard hat is JavaScript based.
我们之所以要使用 Hardhat 是因为 Hardhat 是基于 JavaScript 的
It's a JavaScript based development environment.
这是一个基于 JavaScript 的开发环境
It's got JavaScript based compilation, environment, deploying, testing, debugging.
它有基于 JavaScript 的编译环境，部署，测试，bug 调试
Now, for those of you who love TypeScript,
现在，对于那些喜欢 TypeScript 的人来说
we will also have TypeScript editions of every single one of our code examples for you.
我们在每一个代码示例中也会为你们添加 TypeScript 版本
So if you love JavaScript, we got you,
所以，如果你喜欢 JavaScript，我们为你准备了
if you love TypeScript, we also got you
如果你喜欢 TypeScript，我们同样为你提供
we're not always going to walk through us doing the TypeScript. But we will sometimes,
我们并不总是会完整执行 TypeScript 的流程，但有时会这样做
and all of the code for the TypeScript will be available in the GitHub repo.
并且所有 TypeScript 的代码都会放到 Github 仓库里
Now, before we can actually learn hard hat,
现在，在我们真正开始学习 Hardhat 之前
we have to learn another package first.
我们需要先学习一些其他程序包
So we're going to learn how to do everything with ethers. Jas,
我们要学就是如何使用 ethers.js
which is a JavaScript based library for working with smart contracts.
这是一个基于 JavaScript 的库，用于编写智能合约
And it's also what powers the next tool that we're going to be working with, which is hard hat
这也是我们要使用的下一个工具的基础，就是 Hardhat
under the hood of hard hat. There's a lot of ethers Jas.
Hardhat 的底层使用了很多 ethers.js 的东西
So it's important for us to learn ethers Jas
所以对我们来说学习 ethers.js 非常重要
so that we can understand what hard hat is actually doing.
这能够让我们理解 Hardhat 实际上是如何工作的
Now for the rest of the course,
在接下来的课程中
I'm going to be using a code editor called Visual Studio code.
我将使用名为 Visual Studio Code 的代码编辑器
This is one of the most powerful code editors on the planet.
这是地球上最强大的代码编辑器之一
And if you've already got it set up, feel free to go ahead and skip this part.
如果这部分你已经配置好了，那你可以跳过这里
If you already have a professional coding setup
如果你已经做好了某些专业的代码配置
with no GS and VS code, and Git and everything,
比如 node.js 和 VS code 还有 Git 等等
feel free to use the timestamps in the GitHub repository. To skip over this setup section.
请根据 Github 仓库中的时间戳，按照自己的需要跳过这些配置环节
You'll often hear people refer to this as
你经常可以听到别人这样称呼这个工具
VS code, or Visual Studio code or just Visual Studio.
VS code 或 Visual Studio Code 或者干脆就是 Visual Studio
However, it's important to note that Visual Studio code this is different than Visual Studio,
然而，一个很重要的事是，这个 Visual Studio Code 和 Visual Studio 是不一样的
which you might see look like this.
就是你现在看到的这个
So Visual Studio code is what you want, not Visual Studio,
所以，你要用的 Visual Studio Code 而不是 Visual Studio
Visual Studio is a different application,
Visual Studio 是完全不同的另一个应用
make sure you're on Visual Studio code.
请确保你使用的是 Visual Studio Code
Now, if you choose so and you're a total Harto, you can absolutely work just with your terminal,
如果你是一个真正的高手并且你想的话，你可以完全只用终端进行工作
or just with PowerShell, or just with whatever coding environment that you want, like atom or Sublime.
或者是 PowerShell，或者是任何你想用的代码环境，比如 Atom 或者 Sublime
However, for us, we're going to be working with Visual Studio code.
不过，我们要使用的只有 Visual Studio Code
And I'm going to be going through setting up Visual Studio code
并且我设置 Visual Studio Code 的时候
the way that I like to set it up,
会按照我个人的偏好来进行设置
you can actually set it up whatever way that you feel comfortable.
而你完全可以按照自己的偏好来设置
And of course, in our lesson six here,
当然，在我们的 Lesson 6 这里
we have a link to installation and setup.
我们放了一个指导安装和配置的链接
And I'm going to be adding more links as we go about here.
之后这里还会添加更多的链接
And once again, all the code that we're going to be working with is in this GitHub repository down here where it says code.
再次提示，我们要处理的所有代码都会放到这个 Github 仓库里，代码就在这下面
Now we're gonna go through three different installation processes
现在我们会介绍三种不同的安装流程
and pick the one that's most appropriate for you.
选择一个适合你的就好
The first one is going to be for Mac and Linux users.
第一种是面向 Mac 和 Linux 用户的
The second one is going to be for Windows users.
第二种是面向 Windows 用户的
And then our third one is going to be a last ditch effort.
而第三种将作为一种最后的手段
If for whatever reason, you can't get Windows or Linux or the Mac instructions to work,
无论出于什么原因，如果你无法获得 Windows 或 Linux 或 Mac 系统进行作业的话
we're going to use a Git pod installation.
我们将使用 Gitpod 进行安装
Now, I highly, highly recommend that you try to get everything working locally without using Git pod.
我非常非常建议你尝试在本地进行所有工作而不是使用 Gitpod
However, if for whatever reason,
然而，如果是出于某种原因
you can't get those installation pieces to work,
你不能使用那些安装方式的话
we will have Git pod instructions
我们会对 Gitpod 进行必要的说明
for all of the repos that we work with here.
对于我们这里要使用的所有仓库都是
But to get started, we'll start with the Mac and Linux installation instructions.
接下来让我们从在 Mac 和 Linux 上安装开始讲起